no way
绝不
one day
有一天
in game
在游戏里
I can meet someone who is right for me.
我可以遇到一个适合我的人。
The scene when I first met her
第一次见到她的场景
I will never forget it in my life
我一生都不会忘记
sea ​​knight
海骑士
you are my partner
你是我的伙伴
You can call me Bai
你可以叫我白
This task is
这个任务是
Playing a spy couple
饰演一对间谍情侣
Let’s go through this information together.
让我们一起来了解一下这些信息。
What is the problem?
有什么问题？
Are you really human?
你真的是人类吗？
Or is it a game character?
或者它是一个游戏角色？
Be careful
当心
You've just
你刚才
No one is more suitable than me
没有人比我更适合
Cannot be a partner
不能成为合作伙伴
Yes
是的
Come quickly
快来
Both of us
我们俩
in action
在行动
forever and ever
永永远远
The idea is
我们的想法是
always stay tuned
永远保持关注
if we are together
如果我们在一起
I'm very confident
我非常有信心
do you know?
你知道吗？
you don't hate me
你不恨我
so frustrating
真令人沮丧
Don't you want to talk?
你不想说话吗？
you are very introverted
你很内向
Low emotional intelligence
情商低
eight eight eight nine nine
八八八九九
You know
你懂的
You have low emotional intelligence
你情商低
when the time comes
在时机成熟时
Home
家
I'm going to see Supe.
我要去见苏佩。
I'll take you there
我会带你去那
How are you
你还好吗
I can go alone
我可以一个人去
I'll take you there
我会带你去那
ruler
统治者
How are you?
你还好吗？
How are you
你还好吗
be careful be careful
小心点 小心点
Sope
索佩
Xiangyang
乡阳
conduct
进行
I'm here?
我在这？
what did you do today?
今天你做了什么？
talk to me
跟我说话
I want to see
我想看看
and
和
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Your mouth feels so sweet today
今天你的嘴感觉好甜
OK?
好的？
i like you like this
我喜欢你这样
I prepared a surprise
我准备了惊喜
What surprise?
什么惊喜？
For you
为你
I have prepared two tickets.
我准备了两张票。
It’s been a long time since I’ve performed in Jinhai.
好久没来金海演出了。
Would you like to go to the opera with me?
你想和我一起去看歌剧吗？
I am
我是
Our first meeting was
我们的第一次见面是
it makes sense
它有意义
let's go
我们走吧
ruler
统治者
how?
如何？
Have you thought about it seriously?
你有认真思考过吗？
Why are you in such a hurry?
你为什么这么急？
between us
我们之间
I wish we could be closer
我希望我们能更接近
let us do this
让我们这样做
I will entertain you when you come to Zhenhai
当你来镇海时我会招待你
But I'm not in Zhenhai
但我不在镇海
I can't promise now
我现在无法承诺
How are you
你还好吗
come to me
过来找我
I'll buy you a plane ticket
我给你买张机票
I'm a little busy these days
我这几天有点忙
I think I don't have time
我想我没有时间
Then
然后
I will fly away
我会飞走
I'll give my boss a day off tomorrow.
明天我就给老板放一天假。
Now
现在
I don't think this is a good opportunity to meet
我不认为这是一个见面的好机会
I don't know you very well yet
我对你还不太了解
If we meet accidentally
如果我们不经意的相遇
You may ruin each other's good impression.
你可能会破坏彼此的好印象。
I have many friends around me
我身边有很多朋友
Let me introduce my girlfriend.
我介绍一下我的女朋友。
No one supports my online relationship
没有人支持我的网络关系
it's too hard
这太难了
Then
然后
So are you going to give up on me?
那么你要放弃我吗？
of course not
当然不是
At least
至少
we must meet first
我们必须先见面
so far i
到目前为止我
that's right
这是正确的
these feelings
这些感受
do you understand?
你明白吗？
in this feeling
在这种感觉中
I have no idea
我不知道
I feel unsafe
我感觉不安全
of course i understand
我当然明白
I can always feel your emotions
我总能感受到你的情绪
i am in this world
我在这个世界上
I am the person who knows you best
我是最了解你的人
Sope
索佩
What's wrong?
怎么了？
I'm considering your offer
我正在考虑你的报价
do you have a boyfriend?
你有男朋友吗？
No
不
I only have you
我只有你
but you have never seen me
但你从未见过我
I have no idea
我不知道
are you serious about me?
你对我是认真的吗？
this
这
Everything is only in a moment
一切只在一瞬间
What did we talk about before?
我们之前谈了什么？
Do you remember everything?
你还记得一切吗？
Of course I remember
我当然记得
Last time here
上次来这里
what did i wear
我穿了什么衣服
white suit
白色西装
There is a scarf on the left chest.
左胸前有一条围巾。
I still have a pocket watch hanging on my chest.
我胸前还挂着一块怀表。
our first meeting
我们第一次见面
What was the fifth sentence I said?
我说的第五句话是什么？
I'm a rookie
我是新秀
I am looking forward
我很期待
The day the relationship was confirmed
确定关系的那一天
how is the weather?
天气怎么样？
incheon
仁川
no wind
没有风
The sunset is beautiful
夕阳很美
first
首次
This was the first time I met someone with a good memory.
这是我第一次见到记忆力好的人。
Because Su Pei likes you
因为苏佩喜欢你
with you
与你
every moment
每一个瞬间
I remember them all
我都记得
you are really interested in me
你真的对我感兴趣
I'm surprised
我很惊讶
Then do a lot of tasks
然后做很多任务
repay me
报答我
Yes
是的
I got it now
我现在知道了
meet me
跟我碰面
This is for you
这是给您的
There is definitely a certain degree of difficulty
难度肯定是有一定的
do not be angry
别生气
No, I'm not angry.
不，我没有生气。
only
只是
I
我
I feel like I know you better
我感觉我对你的了解更深了
I'm glad you understand me.
我很高兴你能理解我。
It's too late
也已经晚了
I go first
我先去
Hello
你好
Good night
晚安
love poems
爱情诗
this is a program
这是一个程序
How do you recognize love poetry?
你如何认识爱情诗？
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
No
不
How do you play this game?
你是怎么玩这个游戏的？
so interesting
好有趣
Why would you put this in my game?
你为什么要把这个放到我的游戏里？
that that that that
那个那个那个
Two people
两个人
I want to introduce you to you.
我想把你介绍给你认识。
What did you say?
你说什么？
calm down.
冷静，冷静。
Now
现在
you're drunk
你醉了
you will be in the game
你会在游戏中
when you enter the game
当你进入游戏时
so
所以
I want you two to meet.
我想让你们两个见面。
just like you
就像你一样
we chatted for a while
我们聊了一会儿
Because I don't want to see Soppai
因为我不想见到Soppai
Why do you always force me?
你为什么老是强迫我？
I'm going to force it
我要强迫它
That's because I want to help you
那是因为我想帮助你
I don't need your help
我不需要你的帮助
I want you
我要你
I thought you wanted to see me
我以为你想见我
everyone
每个人
I won't do it like you
我不会像你那样做
Just meet him once in the game
只要在游戏中遇见他一次
I am very satisfied
我很满意
yourself
你自己
Don't you think you're cheating yourself?
你不觉得你在欺骗自己吗？
if i really have feelings for you
如果我真的对你有感觉
Why do I refuse to see you?
我为什么拒绝见到你？
she has a reason
她有一个理由
I give you freedom
我给你自由
It doesn't give you freedom, does it?
它不会给你自由，不是吗？
you can't help it
你情不自禁
anyway i
无论如何我
What does it have to do with you?
跟你有什么关系？
Why bother us?
何必打扰我们呢？
I want to help
我想帮忙
I treat you as a friend
我把你当朋友
Bai Ke obviously cheated on you.
白克显然欺骗了你。
What did I ask you to do?
我让你做什么了？
Did I ask you to do something you shouldn't do?
我有叫你做不该做的事吗？
No matter what, you have to buy money
无论如何都要买钱
pretend how you feel
假装你的感受
you can't continue
你不能再继续了
I can't let her go
我不能让她走
for her
为了她
I've tried too much
我已经尝试了太多
I am honest
我是真诚的
Let's stop talking about feelings
我们别再谈感情了
you may not even realize you
你甚至可能没有意识到自己
Are you a computer person too?
你也是电脑人吗？
you know very well
你很清楚
This is Sope
这是索佩
maybe not human
也许不是人类
let us think
让我们想想
forward
前
We have been in contact for so long
我们已经联系这么久了
sad and
悲伤和
Do you feel angry?
你有愤怒的感觉吗？
I
我
Why should I make her sad?
我为什么要让她伤心？
if we are all happy together
如果我们都幸福地在一起
not good?
不好？
It's just an emotionless show.
这只是一个没有感情的节目。
Match your fictional character
匹配您的虚构角色
I do not know what you're talking about
我不知道你在说什么
OK
好的
Then let me ask you
那我问你
the last time
最后一次
when we meet on the edge of a cliff
当我们在悬崖边相遇
What clothes are you wearing
你穿什么衣服
Why am I writing this?
我为什么要写这个？
I
我
I'll ask again
我再问一下
you two
你们俩
when we first met
在我们第一次见面的时候
What is the fifth word?
第五个字是什么？
What exactly do you want to express?
你到底想表达什么？
What I want to say is
我想说的是
This little problem
这个小问题
It’s ok if you can’t answer
如果您无法回答也没有问题
others
其他的
I can't answer
我无法回答
But I can do it.
但我能做到。
because it is a program
因为它是一个程序
every little detail
每一个小细节
I record it all
我全部记录下来
I can answer all your questions
我可以回答你所有的问题
I can also answer
我也可以回答
This is the chat record
这是聊天记录
I'll find it for you
我会帮你找到的
Xiangyang
乡阳
don't deceive yourself
别欺骗自己
she just
她只是
This is an emotionless show.
这是一个没有感情的节目。
she is by my side
她在我身边
Because it's worth using
因为它值得使用
i'm using you
我在利用你
love poems
爱情诗
this is a program
这是一个程序
How to read love poems?
怎样才能读懂爱情诗呢？
Is it a real person?
是否是真人
who cares
管他呢
please please
拜托拜托
Don't disturb us
别干扰我们
Xiangyang
乡阳
go out
出去
listen to me
听我说
leave
离开
No
不
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
Xiangyang's superior
香阳的上级
Not a real person?
不是一个真实的人吗？
It was edited on a computer.
它是在电脑上编辑的。
AI
人工智能
That's right, artificial intelligence
没错，人工智能
on your phone
在你的手机上
voice assistant
语音助手
But this store
但这家店
than voice assistant
比语音助手
It's so much more luxurious
真是豪华多了
Can imitate human thinking
可以模仿人类思维
with humans
与人类
Very lively and good at communication
非常活泼、善于沟通
simple human emotions
人类简单的情感
Please reply
请回复
Still, it's a program.
尽管如此，它仍然是一个程序。
If your mood is a bit complicated
如果你的心情有点复杂
I can't answer
我无法回答
this is what i noticed
这就是我注意到的
So online
所以在网上
I can't find her picture
我找不到她的照片
I can't even find the truth
我什至找不到这个真相
Xiangyang
乡阳
Why do you like this show?
你为什么喜欢这个节目？
You don’t know the world of men
你不知道男人的世界
This is a special attack game
这是一款特殊的攻击游戏
this is a terrible place
这是一个可怕的地方
in virtual world
在虚拟世界中
No real contact required
不需要真正的接触
You can control many players
你可以控制很多玩家
if you say so
如果你这么说
we are
我们是
You can't criticize Xiangyang's superiors.
你不能批评向阳的上级。
But this time, I went to Xiangyang’s house,
但这一次，我去了香阳家，
It’s not without gain.
也不是没有收获。
Go back and look at this
回去看看这个
What?
什么？
This is Xiangyang
这里是香阳
This is a love poem written for that fictional character.
这是一首为那个虚构人物写的情诗。
Remember what I said?
还记得我说过的话吗？
Xiangyang likes to write English poems.
向阳喜欢写英文诗。
This is Sope
这是索佩
if it is a program
如果它是一个程序
Why Xiangyang?
为什么是香阳？
Did I ask you to write a love poem?
我有叫你写一首情诗吗？
What is the secret of love poetry?
爱情诗的秘密是什么？
i move on
我继续前进
I can't find any evidence of leaks to Yang Yang.
我找不到任何向阳泄密的证据。
What message are you conveying?
你传达了什么信息？
To Supe?
到苏佩？
if
如果
Couldn't this secret exist in love poetry?
这个秘密难道就不能存在于爱情诗中吗？
Why are you looking at me like this?
你为什么这样看着我？
never
决不
Am I not talking nonsense?
我这不是废话吗？
No
不
this time
这次
I think this makes sense.
我认为这是有道理的。
No praise
不表扬
I have something else to say
我还有话要说
Why?
为什么？
Do you also know that Xiangyang?
你也认识那个香阳吗？
Sope
索佩
This is called artificial intelligence.
这就是所谓的人工智能。
I can't help it
我情不自禁
When operating a computer
操作电脑时
I just woke up
我刚睡醒
I have no choice but to explain
我别无选择只能解释
How do you feel now?
你现在感觉怎么样？
I was definitely emotionally shattered.
我的情绪肯定已经崩溃了。
maybe in the future
也许在将来
I won't believe Bai
我不会相信白
So about Ye Wu
那么关于夜雾
If Xiangyang knew the truth
如果香阳知道真相的话
I won't work anymore
我不会再工作了
Not worth using anymore
不值得再使用了
then you can grab it
然后你就可以抓住它
brother
兄弟
actually
实际上
poor
贫穷的
i can't forgive you
我无法原谅你
Unless he is a spy
除非他是间谍
we can be real friends
我们可以成为真正的朋友
you
你
Don't be too emotional
不要太情绪化
Huang Zicheng
黄子成
lie
说谎
Why did you lie to me?
你为什么要骗我？
why why
为什么为什么
Sope
索佩
I'm here?
我在这？
I'm just telling you that we meet again
我只是告诉你我们又见面了
Don't you feel uncomfortable?
你不觉得难受吗？
Why do you feel bad?
你为什么感觉不好？
You are the person I most care about
你是我最在乎的人
but I
但是我
I did something to repel you.
我做了一些事情来排斥你。
Don't you care at all?
你一点也不关心吗？
My love to you
我对你的爱
You can block all negative emotions
你可以屏蔽一切负面情绪
you should be angry
你应该生气
you will feel bad
你会感觉很糟糕
I did something that made you feel bad.
我做了一些让你感觉不好的事。
I must be in a bad mood.
我一定心情不好。
like a normal person
像一个正常人一样
please react
请反应
are you mad at me?
你气死我了？
I won't pay attention to you
我不会搭理你
sorry
对不起
i need some
我需要一些
I apologize
我道歉
How are you
你还好吗
I have forgiven you
我已经原谅你了
Can we reconcile?
我们可以和解吗？
Do you really like me?
你真的喜欢我吗？
of course i like you
我当然喜欢你
Why did you ambush me?
你为什么要伏击我？
What did Bai Ke do wrong?
白克做错了什么？
victory
胜利
I defeated player Soppai
我打败了玩家 Soppai
How is this going?
这是怎么回事？
Xiangyang canceled her game account.
香阳注销了她的游戏账号。
when?
什么时候？
Now
现在
he himself
他自己
I solved my partner's life
我解决了我伴侣的生活
why suddenly
为什么突然
Is it so violent?
有这么暴力吗？
I asked to meet Suppai.
我要求与 Suppai 见面。
i was rejected
我被拒绝了
If you look at the conversation
如果你看一下对话
he is a chef
他是一名厨师
I realized it wasn't a real person.
我发现那不是一个真人。
OK
好的
one day will come
总有一天会到来
faster than expected
比预期的要快
a weak person
一个软弱的人
My personality suddenly changed
我的性格突然变了
There must be other situations
一定还有其他情况
Have you found out Huang Zicheng's identity?
你查到黄子成的身份了吗？
I haven't found it yet
我还没找到
I still need some time
我还需要一些时间
I already have enough time with you
我已经有足够的时间陪你了
I have no idea
我不知道
Do you work for the National Security Agency?
你在国家安全局工作吗？
Or did you do it for yourself?
或者你是为自己做的？
OK
好的
Then I'll give you another 3 days.
那我再给你3天时间。
Yes
是的
OK
好的
bad guy
坏人
they are all bad people
他们都是坏人
Xiangyang
乡阳
How are you?
你还好吗？
Sope and I broke up.
我和索佩分手了。
I can't do this anymore
我不能再这样做了
When I look at her face now
当我现在看着她的脸时
It's disgusting
那真令人恶心
Thank you Huang Zicheng
谢谢黄子成
Why?
为什么？
Why do you have to do this?
为什么你必须这样做？
Why
为什么
Have you been exposed?
你暴露了吗？
I just want you to wake up
我只是想让你清醒过来
I will kill you
我会杀了你
kill it
杀了它
Xiangyang
乡阳
Xiangyang, wake up.
香阳，你醒醒吧。
Kill you
杀了你
you ruined everything
你毁了一切
I kill you
我杀了你
I
我
Xiangyang
乡阳
Kill you
杀了你
security guard security guard
保安员 保安员
There's a fight going on here.
这里有人在战斗。
Come on come on
快来快来
I'm going to kill you I'm going to kill you
我要杀了你 我要杀了你
Xiangyang
乡阳
if you kill someone
如果你杀了人
Your life is over
你这辈子就完了
Kill you
杀了你
Xiangyang
乡阳
wake up
清醒过来
i killed it
我杀了它
I
我
kill it
杀了它
What's wrong?
怎么了？
Report now
立即举报
no no
不，不
There were some misunderstandings before.
之前有一些误会。
already solved
已经解决了
wake up quickly
快点醒来
Don't embarrass me here
别在这里让我难堪
hand
手
How are you?
你还好吗？
How are you
你还好吗
I do it by myself
我自己做的
where to
去那里
Can you pack it for me?
你能帮我包一下吗？
let's go
我们走吧
Thanks
谢谢
sorry
对不起
don't feel sad
不必感到难过
Like venting anger.
就像发泄愤怒一样。
I didn't expect it at all
我根本没想到
I didn't know things would turn out like this
我不知道事情会变成这样
Actually in my heart
其实在我心里
I knew it
我就知道
White is
白是
you are not alone
你并不孤单
You've just
你刚才
I just don't want to pretend I don't know
我只是不想假装我不知道
i move on
我继续前进
I want to continue being stupid like this
我想继续这样傻下去
but why
但为什么
Are you sure you want to expose it?
你确定要曝光吗？
even if it's not me
即使不是我
one day i will wake up
有一天我会醒来
nobody
没有人
You can't live in a fantasy world
你无法生活在一个奇幻的世界里
I just
我只是
I wish someone was by my side
我希望有人在我身边
That is
那是
in a fantasy world
在一个奇幻的世界里
But this companionship
但这份陪伴
It takes a lot of effort
需要付出很大的努力
ask yourself
问你自己
Do you think it's worth it?
你觉得值得吗？
Not worth that much
不值那么多
true love
真正的爱情
I don't want anything in return
我不想要任何回报
But dating
但约会
This store is different
这家店不一样
The companionship given to her is
给予她的陪伴是
Display prices accurately
准确显示价格
through various conditions
通过各种条件
I must satisfy you
我必须满足你
for you
给你
I gave it a pre-existing meaning.
我赋予了它一个预先存在的意义。
But I'm in too deep
但我陷得太深了
i can't recover
我无法挽回
Why can't I transfer it back?
为什么我不能把它转回来？
own fault
自己的错
if i realize
如果我意识到
it's never too late
永远不会太迟
i can make up for it
我可以弥补
Do you know what I did?
你知道我做了什么吗？
Tell me I can make it up to you
告诉我我可以弥补你
what have you done?
你做了什么？
I stole confidential information.
我窃取了机密信息
i can't make up for it
我无法弥补
Even if the world collapses
就算世界崩塌
I don't want to live anymore
我也不想活了
This is just a virtual world
这只是一个虚拟世界
The you now is the real you
现在的你就是真正的你
you must be strong
你一定要坚强
you can save yourself
你可以救自己
It's too late to say anything now
现在说什么都晚了
own fault
自己的错
As long as you realize your mistakes
只要你认识到自己的错误
There is still room for compensation.
还有弥补的余地。
How can I compensate?
我该如何补偿？
Go to embroidery
去绣花
embroidery?
刺绣？
willingly
自愿地
If you actively cooperate with the investigation,
如果你积极配合调查，
I can reduce your sentence
我可以给你减刑
I have a chance to start over
我有机会重新开始
real
真的
stop avoiding it
不要再回避它
no matter which path you choose
无论你选择哪一条路
as your friend
作为你的朋友
I have no right to interfere with you
我没有权利干涉你
but you
但是你
I hope we can face it positively
希望我们能积极面对
so that
以便
you can escape this trap
你可以逃脱这个陷阱
I know?
我知道？
your own fault
你自己的错
must face
必须面对
real
真的
I can use this shade to cut
我可以用这个阴影来切割
your life
你的生命
we can start over
我们可以重新开始
Can we really start over?
我们真的可以重新开始吗？
let's go together
咱们一起去吧
how?
如何？
Are the results out?
结果出来了吗？
The language of this love letter is
这封情书的语言是
The error has occurred several times
错误已经发生好几次了
Through these errors we
通过这些错误我们
Arrange and combine again
再次排列组合
I got a new password
我得到了一个新密码
finally
终于
everywhere
到处
it represents all numbers
它代表所有数字
I've already contacted you
我已经联系过你了
I contacted Biota's secret location.
我联系了生物群的秘密地点。
this number
这个号码
Their experimental data and
他们的实验数据和
exact match
完全匹配
you can almost check
你几乎可以检查
Suspect possesses secret data
嫌疑人拥有秘密数据
Hidden in love letters
藏在情书里
Continue delivery
继续交货
Very high concealment
隐蔽性非常高
Now I have proof
现在我有证据了
Xiangyang
乡阳
Can you arrest me?
你能逮捕我吗？
Yanagawa
柳川
Organize data
整理数据
Immediately request Xiang Yang’s arrest.
立即请求逮捕向阳。
Yes
是的
Hello
你好
brother
兄弟
take me there now
现在带我去
Can you call it embroidery?
你能称之为刺绣吗？
if he
如果他
If we can cooperate
如果可以合作的话
you can call it embroidery
你可以称之为刺绣
Thanks
谢谢
Huang Zicheng
黄子成
I advised Xiang Yang to surrender.
我劝项阳投降。
a good job
好工作
go to hospital
去医院
don't get infected
不要被感染
OK
好的
Hello
你好
Are you busy today?
你今天忙吗？
How are you
你还好吗
Then let's have dinner together tonight.
那我们晚上一起吃饭吧。
I have an appointment
我有一个预约
tonight
今晚
Lao Huang asked me to go home for dinner.
老黄叫我回家吃饭。
OK
好的
I'll hang up the phone
我会挂断电话
Wait a moment
等一下
sorry
对不起
Why?
为什么？
Let's have dinner together tomorrow
明天我们一起吃饭吧
choose a place
选择一个地方
I have something to say
我有话要说
How is this going?
这是怎么回事？
let's meet and talk
让我们见面谈谈
OK
好的
Then see you tomorrow
那么明天见
This is what happened
事情是这样发生的
I was taken advantage of in a game
我在游戏中被利用了
By continuing to write love letters
通过继续写情书
give them
给他们
We will provide you with research data from our company
我们将为您提供我们公司的研究数据
We will send you an email
我们会向您发送一封电子邮件
I found it
我找到了
more than a love letter
不仅仅是一封情书
Every letter hides a secret
每封信里都藏着一个秘密
Just the way Soppai taught me
按照 Soppai 教我的方式
I entered my password
我输入了密码
hidden in english poetry
隐藏在英语诗歌中
send
发送
This is what Suppai gave me.
这是 Suppai 给我的。
secret plan
秘密计划
I copied it to USB
我把它复制到USB
through this
通过这个
I can find hidden data in seconds
我可以在几秒钟内找到隐藏的数据
Is there anything else you're hiding?
你还有什么隐瞒的事吗？
I've told you everything
我已经告诉你一切了
I am
我是
I don't want to live in a fantasy that deceives myself
我不想活在欺骗自己的幻想里
I will face my mistakes
我会面对我的错误
This is how my life has become
我的生活就这样变成了
we can start over
我们可以重新开始
your espionage
你的间谍活动
must be punished by law
必须受到法律制裁
But the attitude of surrender
但投降的态度
very good
非常好
Do my best
尽我所能
I will help you
我会帮你
Please see the situation
请看情况
Thanks
谢谢
What about ophthalmology?
眼科呢？
What about the technical department?
技术部呢？
Pass this program on to her
把这个程序传给她
Write a love letter quickly
快快写进情书
secret data
秘密数据
OK
好的
Yes
是的
Thanks
谢谢
If Xiangyang suddenly quits the game
如果香阳突然退出游戏
Spies are always suspicious.
间谍总是会起疑心。
So embroidery is
所以刺绣是
you must keep a secret
你必须保守秘密
I have joined the biology group
我已经加入生物组了
i spoke to you
我跟你说过话
Unified through external sightseeing
通过外部观光统一
Xiang Yang was in a strange mood.
向阳的心情很奇怪。
I resign and go home
我辞职回家
I'm a gamer again
我又变回游戏玩家了
I looked into this particular assignment.
我调查了这个特殊任务。
so long
这么久
I feel like I'm losing my power
我感觉我正在失去力量
behind this game
这场比赛的背后
how many spies are there
有多少间谍
How many people are there?
还有多少人
Was he captured by spies?
难道他被间谍抓走了？
They are digging out these spies one by one.
他们正在将这些间谍一一挖出来。
When will it end?
什么时候结束？
this is our job
这是我们的工作
no matter how many
无论有多少
Individually
单独地
i have to find it
我必须找到它
I think
我认为
How to monitor
如何监视
Have they found these players?
他们找到这些玩家了吗？
This is a problem
这是个问题
them
他们
in what way
以什么方式
this
这
You can find available players
您可以找到有空的玩家
And the hit rate is so high.
而且命中率还这么高。
Here, unconditionally
在此，无条件
There must be a mechanism for selecting people
一定要有选人的机制
you say
你说
This could serve as a direction for investigation.
这可以作为调查的一个方向。
If you can't stop the game
如果你无法停止游戏
if we can find the spy
如果我们能找到间谍
If you could choose a gamer
如果你可以选择一个游戏玩家
That
那
What a big gain
真是一个大收获
if i could find this way
如果我能找到这条路
Special Attack Game Weaknesses
特殊攻击游戏的弱点
You can find the weak points of the special attack game.
您可以找到特殊攻击游戏的弱点。
what are you saying?
你在说什么？
I'm talking about a case.
我说的是一个案例。
Director Jin
金总监
Please expand your thinking
请扩展你的思维
Yes
是的
Then
然后
excuse me
打扰一下
Scrap Metal Group Tender Documents
废金属集团招标文件
I have submitted
我已经提交了
our loss
我们的损失
Already out
已经出来了
Ye Wu will soon find out
夜雾很快就会发现
Our goal
我们的目标
This is a little different from what he stole.
这和他偷的有点不一样。
The line between saying and doing is
说和做之间的界限是
worthless
毫无价值
They are on vacation now
他们现在正在度假
There was no contact with any suspicious persons.
没有与任何可疑人员接触。
As you can see, we
正如你所看到的，我们
We have no choice but to arrest Tu and June.
我们别无选择，只能逮捕土和朱恩。
Then let's act quickly
那我们就赶紧行动吧
OK
好的